<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>Books on Core Dump</title>
    <link>//localhost:1313/books/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Books on Core Dump</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.141.0</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="//localhost:1313/books/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>On Love</title>
      <link>//localhost:1313/books/1-on-love/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Apr 2016 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>//localhost:1313/books/1-on-love/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;review&#34;&gt;Review&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;The author puts into beautiful verse everything I&amp;rsquo;ve felt and failed to articulate coherently about the complex and elusive phenomenon called love. Through a lengthy exposition of his relationship, from the uncertain beginnings to it&amp;rsquo;s certain demise, the author takes us on a journey of words, wit and wisdom. The author explores in detail the complex underpinnings of love, examining every single influx of emotion at every minute stage, something that is usually relegated to the status of &amp;ldquo;happily ever after&amp;rdquo; in most novels and stories.
The author&amp;rsquo;s shrewd observations and the relative ease with which he picks up each and every emotion and doubt that crosses his mind amidst the whole ordeal make for an interesting read. The nuggets of philosophy strategically interspersed between episodes of his own relationship with Chloe adds to the whole experience.
My copy of the novel is filled with highlights and side notes as I could not believe the efficacy with which the author has put down everything I&amp;rsquo;ve felt and will most likely feel in all relationships. The unsteady beginning, the idolization, the Marxist mentality, the crippling self doubt, all resonated with me. It was as if the author had chosen the incessant commotion in my head as source material for his work.
While the story of the author&amp;rsquo;s relationship is a rather grim one, he ends the book with details of another encounter suggesting that indeed there might still be hope for a better future.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
